Deng-Fa, Yang (Dylan)

Location: Taiwan Telephone: (+886) 918 766 876 Website: https://dylanyang.com/ Email: dylanyang0523@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/DylanYang0523

NPM: https://www.npmjs.com/package/validate-commit-msg-regexp

Professional Profile

An engineer with a proven ability to co-work and make contributions in a team environment. Around 6 years of experience in programming. Having experience with iOS, Android development. Now mainly focusing and learning on web technologies. With a passion for researching the latest technology. Careful and cautious are the biggest character traits of mine but at the same time do not cripple my efficiency and creativity.

Skills

- ReactJs
- ReduxJs
- Javascript
- Git
- GraphQL
- Docker

- NodeJs
- Webpack
- HTML5
- Sass/Css
- PostgreSQL
- Ruby on Rails

- Linux
- GoLang
- Python
- Laravel
- MongoDB

Career Summary

*Jun 2019 - April 2020

Codegiant (Taiwan & SF)
Consultant & Sr.Developer

Outline: Dispatched the jobs properly depended on the timeline and the strong points of the engineers (2 - 5 people). Participated in a part of administration jobs.

Key Deliverables and Responsibilities:

@ Codegiant Platform (site)

- Upgraded platform form ROR v5.2 to v6.0.
- Transformed ROR server from Thin / Unicorn to Puma.
- Replaced team's Git working process with Trunk Based Development.
- Restructured the developing environment with DevOps engineers. (Docker / Linux)
- Refined Git repository size to boost developing speed. (Git / BFG repo-cleaner)
- Refactored the web front-end with react hooks with a more modularized structure.
 (React)
- Refactored a GoLang Git hook middleware with Ruby on Rails. (Git / ROR)

- Replaced the RESTful APIs with GraphQL.
- Debugged our platform such as the Git LFS upload problem, deadlock problem.

@ Talentherder Platform (site)

- Integrated the databases from SQLite and MongoDB to PostgreSQL. (Python / Jupyter Notebook / Docker / Linux / Bash)
- Improved DB search speed by data-flattening and data-indexing. (PostgreSQL)
- Implemented the Boolean Search. (NodeJs / Javascript / PostgreSQL)
- Redesigned APIs with the new ORM library. (NodeJs / Javascript)
- Launched the new system above within three months.

*Jun 2018 - Jun 2019

CatchPlay (Taiwan)

Front-end Engineer

Outline: Participated in the TV series development. Mainly responsible for the payment function on the platform.

Key Deliverables and Responsibilities:

- Co-worked with over 30 members for the feature of TV series, mainly responsible for the keyword search and layout components for front-end.
- Integrated the payment module. (ECPay / LinePay / ...etc / TW / SG / ID)
- Refined the payment to reduce 40 API calls in the initial state, and 15 API calls when a user switches the payment method.
- Co-worked with the team to develop a CMS controlled page to increase the sign-up and paying rate.
- Co-worked with data analysts to track and test data on Google Tag Manager (GTM) platform.

*Mar 2016 - May 2018

Fun.Crea.Free (Taiwan)
Co-Founder

Outline: Acquired the contracts and the chances to partner with several different companies. Negotiated with clients based on maximizing the benefit of both sides.

Key Deliverables and Responsibilities

- Standardized the workflow SOP for the team.
- Conducted demand interviews and demand analysis with clients.
- Worked with designers to produce the design drawings. (Sketch)
- Participated in and developed several projects. (React / Javascript / NodeJs / AWS)

Tech Design (Taiwan)

Web Engineer

Outline: Co-worked with the market and design team to refactor the main site.

Key Deliverables and Responsibilities

- Developed and maintained the official site. (Angular / Javascript)
- Refactored the part of the database schema. (MySQL)
- Organized source code repository. (Git)
- Optimized UI/UX with designers.

*Mar 2015 - Nov 2015

Frankish International (Taiwan)

Web Engineer

Outline: Completed a web project independently.

Key Deliverables and Responsibilities

- Participated in websites design, plan, and develop. (NodeJs)
- Developed in the project independently. (NodeJS / PHP / AngularJS / HTML / SCSS)
- Conducted demand interviews and demand analysis with clients.

*Sep 2013 - Nov 2014

Tiger Party (Taiwan & NYC)

Software Engineer

Outline: Worked with Taiwan and NYC teams.

Key Deliverables and Responsibilities

- Debugged and maintained the Billboard System.
- Developed the electronic marquee feature. (Javascript)
- Participated in and developed several projects. (Android / Xcode / Cordova / PHP / Javascript)
- Provided technical support for our clients.

Education

2009 - 2013

Fu Jen University | Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science and Information Engineering

Languages

- Mandarin (Native)
- English (Good)
- Taiwanese (Fluent)

*Com 2042 Nov 2044